https://www.jdchs.org/privacy-policy/

Main Office: 801-984-7650 AdmissionsHow to ApplyTuitionProspective ParentsExplore the SchoolInternational StudentsContact AdmissionsAcademicsAcademy ProgramsPhilosophy & ExpectationsAP CapstoneCourse CatalogDepartmentsCollege Planning GuideTAL ProgramStudent LifeEvents CalendarCampus LifeAthleticsAthletic CalendarArtsAbout UsAbout Juan Diego Catholic High SchoolAdministrationFaculty & StaffAlumniParent AssociationJuan Diego Catholic SchoolsEmploymentAwardsContact UsAwardsContact UsParents & StudentsCurrent ParentsCurrent StudentsSupport JDCSPrivacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://www.jdchs.org, Juan Diego Catholic High School in Draper Utah is part of the Skaggs Catholic Center, LLC.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.Contact formsWe process requests through email and Google forms submitted as embedded objects in our websiteCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withWe self host a PowerSchool student information system implementation and legally required contact info is contained in house.  Contact info will be used for parent newsletter communication and is processed via Send Grid (https://sendgrid.com/resource/general-data-protection-regulation/).  We also use the RenWeb student information system in some schools (https://www.renweb.com/privacy-policy/) as well as FACTS for tuition management (https://factsmgt.com/privacy-policy/)How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.Google Analytics keeps your browser type, screen size amongst other computer client information, and location data for marketing purposes inside the United States of America.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataEnrolled families can be directly emailed from our student information system PowerSchool and because of Utah state and U.S. federal law we keep that information indefinitely.  We also will extract information from PowerSchool and use a third part emailing firm SendGrid and their GDPR policy is here: https://sendgrid.com/resource/general-data-protection-regulation/.Your contact informationYou are not required to submit any contact information to us but if you want to have an enrolled student we will need applicable contact information.  As for request forms only the minimal amount of contact information is needed to conduct business with the individual who submitted the form.Additional informationHow we protect your dataWe use TLS encryption and so does Google for submission of web forms.  Information submitted into RenWeb and PowerSchool is not stored encrypted but is transmitted over TLS encryption and is only available to school administrators with subsets of relevant information access by teachers and parents/guardians.What data breach procedures we have in placeAffected parties will be informed of any breech (by us or a third party processor) within 72 hours of notificationWhat third parties we receive data fromGoogle Analytics for marketing purposes and for website performance statisticsWhat automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataNone. Admissions & Financial Aid Academics Student Life Parents & StudentsAdmissionsHow to ApplyTuitionProspective ParentsExplore the SchoolInternational StudentsContact AdmissionsStudent LifeEvents CalanderCampus LifeAthleticsArtsAbout UsAbout Juan Diego Catholic High SchoolAdministrationFaculty & StaffAlumniParent AssociationJuan Diego Catholic SchoolsEmploymentAcademicsAcademy ProgramsPhilosophy & ExpectationsAP CapstoneCourse CatalogDepartmentsCollege Planning GuideTAL ProgramParents & StudentsCurrent ParentsCurrent StudentsAwardsContact UsQuick LinksSupport JDCSJuan Diego Catholic High SchoolMain Office: (801) 984-7650 Student Services: (801) 984-7641 Absentee Line: (801) 984-7648 Fax: (801) 984-7601300 East 11800 South Draper, Utah 84020Privacy Policy
